Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/szerweck (LinkedIn) www.porsche.digital (Company)

Top Skills

Vehicles
Automotive
Business Process

Stefan Zerweck

Chief Operating Officer (COO) at Porsche Digital Stuttgart Region

Summary

Stefan Zerweck is Managing Director and Chief Operating Officer (COO) of Porsche Digital GmbH. Founded in 2016, the technology unit is a subsidiary of the Stuttgart-based sports car manufacturer.

Around 200 employees are currently developing new products and business models at nine different locations worldwide. The focus is on innovations for a digital customer experience and technology-based industry solutions.

Before becoming COO, Zerweck was responsible for setting up Porsche AG's digital business platform. Until 2018, the business informatics graduate headed the Daimler subsidiary Mercedes-Benz.io GmbH.

Experience

Porsche Digital
Chief Operating Officer (COO)
April 2019 - Present (3 years 1 month)
Stuttgart und Umgebung, Deutschland

Everything we create is dedicated to a seamless Porsche experience in your everyday life.

Porsche AG
Director Digital Ecosystem
April 2018 - March 2019 (1 year)
Stuttgart und Umgebung, Deutschland

Mercedes-Benz.io GmbH (formerly known as CINTEO GmbH)
Managing Director
August 2015 - March 2018 (2 years 8 months)
Stuttgart Area, Germany

Digital, mobile and mobility: exciting technology fields increasingly merging. At what point will we start calling a car a mobility app? Mercedes-Benz.io designs the answers to the future of smart mobility.

Daimler AG
Senior Manager Digital Experience & Mercedes me
2006 - July 2015 (9 years)

DaimlerChrysler South East Asia Pte Ltd General Manager CRM & Online 2003 - 2006 (3 years)

DaimlerChrysler AG Senior Manager Corporate eBusiness 2000 - 2003 (3 years)

Daimler AG
Manager Corporate Audit
1996 - 2000 (4 years)
Corporate Audit Information Management

Mercedes-Benz AG Strategic Planning and Marketing Heavy Trucks 1995 - 1996 (1 year)

Education

VWA Hochschule für berufsbegleitendes Studium Diplom-Betriebswirt (BA), Wirtschaftsinformatik · (1992 - 1995)